Music
The Doll Festival is coming soon.
We are here at the cooking studio
Baking powder is added here and mixed
It is an emergency
There is no paper to serve as a cup
You have to handle the dough from the bowl
This one is different
Oh, my God.
Oh, no!
Let's take a look at this.
This is not good.
Oh, no!
I could make this in 10 minutes.
Really, really bad. -It's impossible.
I'm a little more skeptical.
No, seriously, it's impossible.
How can this be pudding?
I don't know.
I should mix it more. - What? It's turning to jelly.
So it's not working? -What? What? Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. It's a total fail.
Juice? -I think we got it right.
We're following the recipe.
Oh, yeah, well, we're a little low on ice.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let's start with the right answer. - Yes, sir.
Yes. - I put the milk in the 70-milliliter bowl.
Oh, that's good. - You put it in there.
And 3 grams of gelatin in 2 teaspoons of water.
2 teaspoons of water.
Then 1 tablespoon of sugar. - Yes.
And dissolved matcha in a little water.
And mixed it with 1 tablespoon of milk.
It's good. - It's good. - I doubt it.
It's good, it's good, it's good. - You want to do it?
When the ice gets smaller and thicker... When the ice gets smaller and slows down, take out the ice.
Take out the ice. - It doesn't seem to be slowing down.
You take the ice out and put it in the pudding cup. - Oh, you mean you take the ice out?
I mean, you have to take the ice out. - But it doesn't seem to be getting any thicker.
Oh, yeah, it's gonna be frothy. - Come on.
Now, if you want it to come back... - Oh, no.
If you don't take out the ice, it'll get thinner and thinner. - Yeah.
Sure, it tastes good. - Oh, my God, it's water.
Okay, one more time. Okay. - One more time.
We were talking about making one more batch after the water.
I see. Let's take out the ice.
We'll add gelatin, and here's the important part.
Let's start with the gelatin.
It won't melt if it's too cold.
Put one over here. - Sure, sure, put it in.
It's so cold it won't dissolve.
I'm sure it'll be ready for you soon.
I'd have done it just a little bit better.
I want to keep this smile. I want to keep that smile.
There's only 10 of them, and they're all about as crazy as the top zero.
Quickly, Masai, then quickly, for real.
Here we go. Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
I'm in! I'm in! I'm definitely in!
I'm getting it, I'm getting it, I'm getting it, I'm getting it, I'm getting it.
Quick, mix it up, just ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice.
Ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice, ice.
I think it might fly off a little bit.
One more time, one more time.
Two. - Two is good.
Two is good. Two is good. Two is good.
Chai... that's the first item... that's the first meal.
We don't need the first one. It's perfect.
It's perfect. It's perfect.
I knew it. It's a growing thing down there.
Put it on a cupcake, it's already 70 grams.
This one's already doing great.
I'm trying to do it plus, you know, whipped cream.
Wash all that stuff.Wash all kinds of things.
Let's go with whipped cream
I'm making whipped cream.
Let's put it in.
Here we go.
It doesn't have to be water.
Hold it down.
Not hot water.
That's my hot water, but with cream.
It's a little low.
This is what hot water looks like.
A little more.
It's for the topping, so it's a little firm.
That's right.
Warm.
What kind of lemon was it?
Not too sweet?
What is this?
Isn't whipped cream sweet?
Gurgling.
Oh, we need granulated sugar.
We need sugar.
It tastes like milk.
Granulated sugar is too coarse.
Well, I'll give it a try.
Sweet, sweet, sweet.
It's a bit of a slice and dice.
Maybe add some sugar next time.
How's that? Pretty cute, isn't it?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Tell him what I look like.
Why am I doing this? I don't know why I'm doing this.
I was just thinking, I've never seen strawberries sliced diagonally.
It's novel, isn't it?
But the leftovers...
Eat it.
Bon appétit!
I wonder how to cut strawberries.
Like this? Yes, like that.
Ah! Look closely.
And...
In the eyes.
So, what's it look like?
I'm not looking too hard.
It's good, right?
Wow.
That's what I'm talking about.
I'll have some of this, too.
Oh, wow.
Come on, let's get it down to size.
Go, go, go!
I ordered Masaki ice.
With ice and rice.
I wonder if this will work.
This looks good. It's surprisingly easy.
Will it go on the side?
I can't see.
I can't cut through.
Maybe I can get him to do it.
Let's give it a try.
Oh, no, it's not coming in.
It's not coming in.
Oh, how's that?
Oh, hey! A cup!
Here you go.
Oh!
Oh, there's so much in here.
It's so good! But still, think about how it's gonna puff up.
Do you think it'll puff up? Will it inflate?
Will it deflate?
About an eighth. Yes!
Eight! Eight. That's right. I remember now.
Almost there, right? Just a little bit more.
Can we get it out?
You can't put the toppings on until you're done, right?
All of it, right? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah!
You know, like this, like this, like this to take the air out. Oh, I see. Take it out.
Let's put it in.
Looks good.
Cooking is fun.
But won't this burn?
This bag of hair.
Don't worry, don't worry, don't worry.
You made six molds.
6 molds are ready.
Now that we have 6 molds, we'd like to put them in the oven that we just preheated.
And here we go!
How many minutes? How many minutes? How many minutes?
I'm setting it right now.
Here we go!
Okay. Okay.
Now all we have to do is wait.
Yeah!
Which one is it?
Yay!
All we have to do is wait a few more minutes.
Wait and it's done.
This one's ready.
Oh, well, let him watch.
Together.
Look at him. And he's lying.
Most people are in this position.
They're all in the same position.
One leg up, one leg down, one leg weighted, arms folded. One leg, one leg up, one leg weighted down, arms folded.
Yeah. - Yeah.
No, no, no, no.
I'm serious about the shape, maybe.
I'm serious about the taste.
I think it's really good.
Why do you say that?
What do you mean, "just the taste"?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's not three colors.
No, it's three colors.
There are three colors.
There's four colors.
Mm-hmm.
Hmm?
Four colors?
That's not what I'm getting at.
What do you think, then?
This is perfect.
It's perfect.
Quantity and need
Quantity and necessity.
We did a lot together, didn't we?
But still...
Say it.
I did pretty well for myself.
Yeah, well...
That was quick.
That's fast.
It's sudden.
Everyone's probably...
I'm making a different impression.
You're surprisingly good.
Yes, you are.
Yes, I am.
So...
It's done!
I'm looking forward to working with you. I look forward to working with you.
It's done.
Well, as you can see...
Uh, us.
Yes, sir.
The cupcake group is finished.
Oh, my goodness.
I'm so happy.
Then, what's your name?
Yes, ma'am.
This is...
Oh, shit.
It's cold.
What's that, cupcake?
Cupcake.
Here we go!
With strawberries on the side.
I see...
Oh, it's cold!
Yeah.
Strawberries.
Delicious!
Open the package.
you
in
the
you
you (formerly honorific, now sometimes derog. term referring to an equal or inferior)
moonflower (Ipomoea alba)
is
I don't need it.
You don't even need whipped cream!
It was a lot harder than I thought it would be.
It's super easy.
Oh, it's super easy!
Oh, my God! Uh huh.
So we can all do the same thing.
What did you think? Our cupcakes.
No, they were good, seriously.
But we were just as good.
I'm as good as you.
Yes, you are.
We didn't lose.
There's more, isn't there?
There's our pudding that you forgot about.
We have tri-color pudding.
Yes, sir.
May I?
Here you go.
Toe, toe, toe, toe.
You did it.
Yeah. - Yeah.
This way, sir.
Oh, no, that went well.
This is three-color pudding.
It's a tri-color pudding.
With feeling.
Okay, with green juice.
Aojiru.
This is matcha.
Matcha.
Oseto salad
Milk pudding
And finally...
Yes, sir.
Did you say store-bought pudding?
No, this is...
This is, this is an egg mixture.
Well, it's a proper pudding.
Well, well, well, well. It's a perennial favorite. Well, well, well, well, it's been a beloved taste for years.
I've already been on the
on the market
I'm done.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
These guys...
That's him.
Yes, sir.
It's a commercial product.
All of them?
Yes, sir.
Milk pudding with green tea.
It tasted like milk pudding.
Yes.
Oh, yes, yes
of monopoly agricultural food
Yes, yes, yes
So, the former direct
Cooking Project
Perfect for the Dolls' Festival
Yes ...
It turned out to be a great project, didn't it?
Yes, sir.
So...
Let's all say it was a nice Girls' Festival.
Let's say it was a good Girls' Festival.
Ready?
It was a nice Girls' Festival!